

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Email siyaramray2019@gmail.com

Mobile (+91) 8088850728

Total work experience
11 Years 0 Month

# **KEY SKILLS**

Html5

CSS

Bootstrap

**JSON** 

Node.Js

Express

Redux

Hooks

Jsx

MongoDB

Mean Stack

Ajax

PHP

MySQL

**Codeigniter Framework** 

**JQuery** 

Postman Tool

JIRA Tool

# siyaram ray

Lead UI Developer

## **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Having 11 years experience in web development specializing in skills html4, html5, css3, css2,bootstrap, Angular 12+, Reactjs, hooks, Redux, nodejs, express, mysql, javascript, xml, json, API, mern, web services. Experienced in development, and Web based applications. Well knowledge of Software Development Life Cycle, and well knowledge of module testing and module integration. Well knowledge of errors detecting and finding the bugs. Experience in web maintenance and good understanding in enhancement of requirements. Communicates with customers and offshore team members effectively. Excellent Team Player possessing Good Communication skills

## **EDUCATION**

2008

BCA

Babasaheb Bhimrao Ambedkar University (BBAU), Lucknow

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Sep 2020 -Present

Lead UI Developer

## **Firstenquiry Digital Media**

Working As Lead UI developer, Handling a team of 4 members. Having skills html4, html5, css3, css2,bootstrap, Reactjs, hooks, Redux, nodejs, express, mysql, javascript, xml, json, API, web services. Project is all about health care application. complete in patient and opd patients, billing, pharma, labs, doctor, appointment etc..

Aug 2015 - Sep 2020

**UI** Developer

# Cybotrix Technologies - deployed at client place LG Software Bangalore

Worked as ui developer and deployed at client place LG Software Bangalore. Worked on Internal vendor empanelment project that is complete vendor documentation to on boarding and payroll management. used technologies as HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Angular 13, rest api of nodejs and express js with mysgl database.

Mar 2012 - Aug 2015 Software Engineer

# Jenesystech pvt ltd, and Deputed at client place Cisco System India Pvt . Ltd.

Working as Software Engineer on agile methodology, Communicating with clients 1. Analysis requirements 1. DB design 2. Coding. 3. Module Testing. 4. Module integration 5. Deployment

Sonarqube

Github

Angular 12 to 17

React.js

**TypeScript** 

Javascript

## **OTHER PERSONAL DETAILS**

City

Bengaluru

Country

INDIA

## **HOBBIES**

**Book Reading, Coding** 

## **LANGUAGES**

- HINDI
- ENGLISH

Jan 2011 - Mar 2012 Software Engineer

## **Emart Solutions India Pvt Ltd.**

worked as Software Engineer (PHP/MYSQL Developer)

#### **Proiects**

#### 24 Months

# **Medical Planet**

Medicalplanet.in is stop solutions for all healthcare related need. it has modules for doctor and patient appointment management. it work for clinic as well as big hospitals. it has doctor account management fetures. it includes labs & test for all type of clinical test. any hospital, clinic, lab, delivery partner, investor, vendor as medicine supplier can register and after account verification they can use medicalplanet service as free of cost. its pharma module is unique features any hospital, clinic, or medical store can register and sell the pharma products online. for hospital and clinic staff management is seprate module where super admin can control all access on each account.

#### 30 Months

# **Firstenquiry Digital Media**

Firstenquiry Digital Media is Classified Leads generations platform for B2B and B2C. it has varius modules as education, real estate, home services, office improvement, property management, leads management, leads distributions. the technologies used html, css, bootstrap, javascript, jquery, php, mvc codeigniter, mysql, react redux, angular, nodejs, express

## 18 Months

## **Electric Bike Recharge Station**

Electric Bike Recharge Station - Project All about Electric Bike Charge Process. Calculation of electric consumptions, time durations, price calculations, bill generations, preparing dashboard for Service Partner with charts and graphs month wide daily weekly. Complete Dashboard for super admin with service partner onboarding.

## 14 Months

## **Vendor Empanelment**

Worked AS UI Developer / Full Stack Developer on Internal vendor empanelment project that is complete vendor documentation to on boarding and payroll management. used technologies as HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Angular 13, rest api of nodejs and express js with mysql database.

## 13 Months

## **Smart Class Online Tutoring**

educational software system was developed for south Korea education system. that provide personalized learning experiences to students. they can join to college class online from home. Technologies used HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, Oracle, Java, Moodle LMS Customization. I play my role as php developer handling complete ui design with development and complete report generations

